# Stefan Davidovski





Romen Rolan 17, Skopje



#### **About Me**

Experienced in management and marketing. Strong knowledge of social media.

Able to handle multiple tasks on a daily basis, flexible, reliable and always willing to learn new skills. I want to work with people and I am used to working in a team whilst also being capable of using own initiative.

Very organized person and hard worker. My goal is successful career and personal development.

### Language

■ Macedonian ■ English

#### **Hobbies**

Singing

Traveling

Hiking

## **Personality Skills**

Responsible

People Oriented

Service - focused

Good with short deadlines

Team worker

#### **Education**

2008-2011 High School

SEPUGS Vasil Antevski - Dren Law degree

2011 University

Faculty of law Justinian I, University Ss. Cyril and Methodius

#### **Work Experience**

2015 - 2016 Receptionist

Hotel "Super 8" Skopje

**2016-2018 Freelancer** 

- Upwork
- Affiliate Marketing
- Shopify Sales

2018-2022 CEO, Founder & Co-owner

Monnel LTD.